{
    "id": "17793ab9016542149ca858bfce69d84c",
    "title": "Simple Present Or Present Continuous Tense",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Planting trees is a very good idea because trees ………………….. oxygen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "produce",
                "are producing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………… to spend time with his children.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "likes",
                "is liking"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Students should always try to improve their grades because universities ………………….. those with bad grades.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are not accepting",
                "do not accept"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Clouds ………………….. from evaporated water.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "form",
                "are forming"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "My sister ………………….. at a municipal school.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "teaches",
                "is teaching"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Volcanoes …………………. hot lava into the air when they …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shoot, erupt",
                "shooting, erupting",
                "are shooting, are erupting"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. how to ride a bicycle?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Do you know",
                "Are you knowing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Supriya is an atheist. She …………………… in God.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "does not believe",
                "is not believing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Cows ………………… on grass.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "feed",
                "are feeding"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Although I still have some difficulties in French, I ………………….. much better now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "understand",
                "am understanding"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}